Papa, today I got my first salary. Very good
son. It's time to introduce you to Agent Vinod.
Agent Vinod.
Agent Vinod is the one who stood by us in every problem.
Son, Agent Vinod is the one
who thinks far ahead. When your grandfather was
in the hospital, Agent
Vinod took care of everything. We were very worried.
You don't know how many mistakes your father makes.
He forgets even the smallest details. But
because of Agent Vinod, till date, no mistake has happened.
Agent Pramod was a very good friend of mine.
I also introduced your father to Agent
Vinod. Now, when you come, ask him.
[Music]
Agent Vinod
who stays with you from generation to generation, just like the
relationship between you and your insurance agent.
[Music]